ILR School Department of Organizational Behavior Chairman's Files /4184
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Department of Organizational Behavior Chairman's Files
1964-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Department of Organizational Behavior
/4184
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8036576
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 28, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /4157: ILR School Department of Organizational Behavior Records /4231: Robert Stern Papers /4254: Harrison Trice Additional Books /4310: Lawrence Williams Papers /4312: William Sonnenstuhl Papers /4313: Harrison Trice Papers
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Department of Organizational Behavior
8036576
- McKersie, Dean Robert folder 1, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- McKersie, Dean Robert folder 2, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- On Department ship Memo, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ILR folder 1, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ILR folder 2, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- OB Department Chairmen Meetings and Minutes, 1982-1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Minutes of OB Department Meeting, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Student Administrative Conference, 1974-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ILR Faculty Internal Review Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Ehrenberg, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)